SANTIAGO RAMON

ALVAREZ GOMEZ

• FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Ocolombia, Medellin, 050022
- +573057668478
- stiago4r@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BACHELOR
 UNIVERSIDAD EAFIT, 2022

Software Engineering

LINKS

- GitHub: https://github.com/stiago
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sa ntiago-alvarez-b6a530233/

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Angular
- Firebase
- CSS
- Unity
- Python
- o C++
- C#
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- java
- vba

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English

ABOUT ME

Developer with a background in web, mobile and game development, having 2+ years of practice and leadership building interactive experiences. Disciplined, organized, humble and accessible person. Committed to good morals, continuous learning, innovation and development of optimal solutions.

Great enthusiastic teamwork, considered cautious, assertive, helpful and creative.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER | AUGUST 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022 tigo colombia, remote

- Develop multiple automatitions on microsoft enviroment to resolve delays operational timelaps using excel macros, power-Query (DAX) and Power Automate to deploy software whit a dinamic response compared to a clasic excel usages. deliver quality products and made several on-boarding process to new developers.
- · Mentored team members in development, issues and technical progression.
- Designed a normalyzer to format data-sets as a tool to improve the consumers data ratio and make it more accessible to operational team.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER & CEO | JANUARY 2019 - PRESENT centraldelbarbero.com, medellín

- Developed, launched and managed the commercialization of a successful app along with other engineer using scrum, Firebase and Angular
- Collaborated with other developers to identify and alleviate software errors and inefficiencies.
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.
- \cdot Got over 5,000 downloads, more than 300 users online at the same time and more than 3,000 usd in revenues.

• SHOWCASE SALESMAN | FEBRUARY 2010 - DECEMBER 2013 central de belleza ©, medellín

- Was my first job and become a complete new challenge to me but after the training time i become a successful deal closer, ofcourse i was better selling hair dryer, hair straighteners or ellectrodomestics in general, but not let that limit myself and learn alot of oter products and even lern how to cobine colors to recomend a nail polish or hair dye.
- Perform a social network integration business.